RG 062:131, Town of Southington
Connecticut State Library
Town of Southington records
1792-1989
Connecticut State Library
Southington (Conn.)
150 cubic feet
Administrative, poor relief, land, court, military, school, election, tax, and borough records for the town of Southington.
RG062_131
2007-047
Historical Note
The town of Southington was incorporated in October 1779 and was taken from Farmington. The Borough of Southington was incorporated in 1889. The town and borough consolidated in 1947.
Scope and Content
Series 1. Administrative Records, 1832-1980, contain a variety of material including abatements, agreements an indentures, bonds, selectmen's accounts and correspondence, and financial records. Abatements covering 1732 to1942 list the name and amount of tax abated. By the 1870s the reason for abatement was also listed. Examples include error in original assessment, poverty, removal from town, or the fact that the person was a pensioner or soldier. Town officials were generally bonded and the records contain a number of bonds from 1879 to 1907 mostly for constables, tax collectors, and treasurers. There is also a folder of liquor license applications covering 1917 to 1919. The largest volume of records in series 1 is financial records. These contain various accounts receivable registers, check stubs, journals, ledgers, notes and bills payable, orders, permit registers, receipts and expenditures, and trial balance ledgers. Two volumes of ledgers may be from the municipal store, 1897-1903. These list individuals and items purchased with amounts paid. A group of files labeled "Special Matters" that cover 1951 to 1953 deal with some of the topics found in Series 9, Borough Records for earlier years such as highways, licenses and permits.
The bulk of Series 2. Poor Relief Records, 1909-1922, 1951-1953, is comprised of outside poor ledgers covering 1887 to 1937. Series 3. Land Records, 1877-1959, includes a volume of petitions of foreclosure, 1877-1879, and a survey index listing property owner, date of survey, surveyor, location of property, and map number for surveys performed from 1883 to 1959. Series 4. Court Records, 1858-1961, includes a volume of assignments of wages for 1888 to 1939 and one folder of justice of the peace records, the bulk from 1880 to 1886. Series 5 Military Records, 1869-1940, contain 2 volumes of militia enrollments, 1869-1939 and selective service registration cards and list for 1940. Series 6. School Records, 1846-1944, include school construction records from the early twentieth century and school registers from 1859 to 1882. Each register is for a specific district. Most of the school registers present are for the year 1869-1870 with a few from other years. Series 7. Election records, 1940-1955, consist solely of voting lists. Men and women were listed separately in 1940. From 1946 to 1949 the there were separate lists for District 1 and District 2.
Series 8. Tax Records, 1792, 1899-1989, contains a variety of records including appraisal of personal property, 1948-1953; individual tax lists for years 1899, 1907 and 1956; old age assistance tax, 1936-1946, rate books, 1931-1946; street assessments, 1899; and tax abstracts, 1792, 1917-1989. An single-sheet list for 1792 and another undated list from the same period include separate columns for name, number of polls, and various types of property such as oxen, cows, horses, land divided into several categories, money at interest, and luxury goods such as chaises and watches. The group of abstracts starting with 1917 includes a column for automobile. A separate list was kept for automobiles by 1935.
Series 9. Borough Records, 1890-1970, contain a variety of records that document the urbanization of a town. The Borough of Southington was incorporated in 1889 and consolidated with the town in 1947. Some of the records in this series replicate those in other series that are for the town. Examples are bonds, financial records including journals and ledgers, and tax rate books. A large volume of the records in this series relate to sewer connections and street and sidewalk construction. Records concerning other borough issues are also present including licenses and permits, ordinances, police, street lighting and traffic signals, among other things. A small amount of records dated after the Borough consolidated with the Town was found among the borough records during processing. They remain a part of this series.
Related Material
None.
Index Terms
Alternate Creators:
Connecticut. Justice of the Peace (Southington)
Places:
Southington (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Subjects:
Public welfare -- Connecticut -- Southington; Justices of the peace -- Connecticut -- Southington; Soldiers -- Connecticut -- Southington; School enrollment -- Connecticut -- Southington -- Statistics; School construction -- Connecticut -- Southington; Voting registers -- Connecticut -- Southington; Sewerage -- Connecticut -- Southington; Streets -- Connecticut -- Southington -- Design and construction; Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Southington -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Southington -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Southington -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Southington -- Registers
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Provenance
Two tax abstracts, one dated 1792 and the other undated, were donated to the Connecticut State Library on July 15, 1941 by E.A. Moore of New Britain. These items have been incorporated into the 2007-047 accession. They were previously assigned the temporary accession number of T000971.
Container List
- Series 1. Administrative Records, 1832-1980
  - Abatements
    - 1832-1876, 1 volume (Box 1)
    - 1877-1916, 1 volume (Box 1)
    - 1917-1942, 1 volume (Box 1)
  - Agreements and indentures, 1864-1904 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Annual report, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Bank stock returns, 1883-1897; 1 volume (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bonds (Box 2)
    - Constable, 1879-1906 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Prosecuting attorney, 1905-1906 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Tax collector, 1879-1906 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Town clerk, 1902-1907 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Treasurer, 1879-1907 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Construction permit register (Box 2)
    - A-K, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - L-Z, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Liquor license applications, 1917-1919 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Selectmen
    - Account books
      - 1852-1870, 1 volume (Box 3)
      - 1864-1878, 1 volume (Box 3)
      - 1864-1870 April 16, 1 volume (Box 3)
      - 1870 April 16-1874 September 26, 1 volume (Box 4)
      - 1874 September 26-1878, 1 volume (Box 4)
      - 1937 September 1-1938 August 31, 1 volume (Volume Item 5)
      - 1938 September 1-1939 August 31, 1 volume (Volume Item 6)
      - 1939 September 1-1940 August 31, 1 volume (Volume Item 7)
      - 1941 September 1-1942 August 31, 1 volume (Volume Item 8)
    - Correspondence, 1899-1910; 1 volume (Box 4)
  - Special matters, 1951-1953 (Box 9)
    - Ambulance, new, quotation, 1952 (Box 9)
    - Applications (Box 9)
      - Gasoline stations, used and new car dealers, auto repair & auto junk yards, 1951-1953; 2 folders (Box 9)
      - Erection of commercial buildings and advertising signs, 1952-1953 (Box 9)
    - Audit, 1951 (Box 9)
    - Bids, town owned property, 1951-1952 (Box 9)
    - Board of Selectmen appointments, 1951-1953; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Budget, 1951-1953 (Box 9)
    - Bureau of the census, 1952 (Box 9)
    - Canal Street at intersection with Meriden-Waterbury Tpke., 1952-1953 (Box 9)
    - Claims for damages, 1951-1953; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Compensation insurance, 1951-1953; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Contracts & guarantees, 1951-1953; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Highways (Box 9)
      - Drainage, Belleview Avenue, 1952-1953 (Box 9)
      - Drainage, High St & Factory Square, 1952-1953 (Box 9)
      - Mill St. layout and widening of road, 1952-1953 (Box 9)
      - New developments, bonds filed, for acceptance of new roads, 1952-1953 (Box 9)
      - Equipment accidents, 1951-1952 (Box 9)
      - Shovel, Proposal and purchase, 1953 May 6 (Box 9)
      - Truck, quotations, 1952 (Box 9)
      - Pick-up truck, quotations, 1953 (Box 9)
    - Jury committee, 1952 (Box 9)
    - Jury list, 1953 (Box 9)
    - Licenses, Lodging house or tourist camps, 1951-1953; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Parking meters, 1951-1952 (Box 9)
    - Permits (Box 9)
      - Bingo, fireworks display, etc., 1952-1953 (Box 9)
      - Overhead signs, 1952-1953 (Box 9)
      - Trailers and trailer camps, 1951-1953; 3 folders (Box 9)
    - Petitions from taxpayers to Board of Selectmen, 1951-1953; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Public acts, Interpretation of same, 1953 (Box 9)
    - Public Utilities Commission, 1951-1953; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Reports (Box 9)
      - Committee Concerning Two Tax Payments and Changing Date of Fiscal Year, 1951-1953 (Box 9)
      - Study Commission on Education in Southington, 1952 (Box 9)
      - Public relief cases and expenditures, 1952-1953; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Servicemen's and other tax refunds, 1951-1953; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Receipts, 1953; 3 envelopes (Box 10)
    - Journal vouchers, 1951-1953 (Box 10)
    - Ambulance reports, 1952-1953 (Box 10)
    - Paid bills, 1951-1953 (Box 10)
    - Record of cash turned over to treasurer, 1953 (Box 10)
  - Statistics of certain Branches of Industry as they existed in the Town of Southington, 1845 (Box 117)
  - Town Clerk
    - Bank statements, cancelled checks, and deposit slips, 1960-1962, 1965 (Box 11)
    - Dog registers
      - 1908-1910, 1 volume (Box 12)
      - 1911-1913, 1 volume (Box 12)
      - 1914-1916, 1 volume (Box 12)
      - 1917-1919, 1 volume (Box 13)
      - 1920-1922, 1 volume (Box 13)
      - 1923-1925, 1 volume (Box 13)
    - Receipts, 1936-1942; 1 volume (Box 13)
  - Treasurer
    - Accounts receivable registers
      - 1942-1959, 1 volume (Box 14)
      - 1955 January-1958 January, 1 volume (Box 15)
      - 1958 February-1961 April, 1 volume (Box 15)
      - 1961 May-1965 March, 1 volume (Box 15)
    - Check stubs (Box 15)
      - 1903-1907 (Box 15)
      - The J.D. Bristol Fund account, 1940-1952 (Box 15)
    - Journals
      - 1877-1883, 1 volume (Volume Item 17)
      - 1901-1902, 1 volume (Box 16)
      - 1940-1953 August, 1 volume (Box 16)
      - Other than general funds, 1953 September -1959 June; 1 volume (Box 16)
      - General funds, 1953 September -1959 June; 1 volume (Box 16)
    - Ledgers
      - 1877-1893, 1 volume (Volume Item 18)
      - 1893-1910, 1 volume (Volume Item 19)
      - 1897-1899, 1 volume (Volume Item 33)
        This ledger may be from the municpal store. It shows purchases made by individuals and organizations and cash paid.
      - 1899-1903, 1 volume (Volume Item 34)
      - 1902-1912, 1 volume (Volume Item 20)
      - 1904-1908, 1 volume (Volume Item 21)
      - 1906-1919, 1 volume (Box Item 22)
      - 1919-1935, 1 volume (Volume Item 25)
      - 1907-1940 (Box 24)
      - 1940-1947 (Box 24)
      - 1935-1951, bulk 1935-1937; 1 volume (Volume Item 26)
      - 1923-1935 (Box 23)
      - circa 1924-1937 (Box 23)
      - 1948-1949 (Box 24)
    - Notes and bills payable, 1915-1938; 1 volume (Box 27)
    - Orders (Box 27)
      - 1890-1900, 1 volume (Box 27)
      - 1903-1906, 1 volume (Box 27)
      - 1912-1913, 1 volume (Box 27)
      - 1915-1916, 1 volume (Box 28)
      - 1920-1921, 1 volume (Box 28)
    - Permit registers
      - 1964 July 1-1965 June 30, 1 volume (Box 29)
      - 1965 July 1-1966 June 30, 1 volume (Box 29)
      - 1966 July 1-1967 June 30, 1 volume (Box 29)
      - 1967 July 1-1968 June 30, 1 volume (Box 29)
      - 1973 July 1-1974 December 31, 1 volume (Volume Item 32)
      - 1975 January 1-1977 June 30, 1 volume (Volume Item 30)
      - 1977 July 1-1980 June 30, 1 volume (Volume Item 31)
    - Receipts and expenditures
      - 1898-1908, 1 volume (Box 36)
      - 1907-1936, 1 volume (Volume Item 35)
      - 1951-1952, 1 volume (Box 36)
      - Civil Division, 1953-1960; 1 volume (Box 36)
      - Small Claims Court, 1953-1960; 1 volume (Box 36)
    - Transfer ledger, 1919-1933; 1 volume (Volume Item 37)
    - Trial balance ledger
      - 1913-1920, 1 volume (Volume 38)
      - 1921-1930, 1 volume (Volume 38)
      - 1923-1934, 1 volume (Volume 38)
      - 1927-1933, 1 volume (Volume 38)
  - Unidentified index, undated (Volume 38)
  - Bank stock returns, 1883-1897; 1 volume
- Series 2. Poor Relief Records, 1909-1922, 1951-1953
  - Outside poor ledgers
    - 1887-1910, 1 volume (Volume Item 39)
    - 1921-1931, 1 volume (Volume Item 40)
    - 1921-1931 (Box 41)
    - 1921-1931 (Volume 41)
  - Outside poor ledger and almshouse accounts, 1919-1937; 1 volume (Volume Item 42)
  - Meeting notice for Board of Relief, 1910 (Box 43)
  - Reports of Board of Relief, 1909-1922 (Box 43)
  - Public relief cases and expenditures, 1951-1953 (Box 117)
- Series 3. Land Records, 1877-1959
  - Unidentified index, undated; 1 volume (Box 43)
  - Petition of forclosure, 1877-1879; 1 volume (Volume Item 45)
  - Survey index, 1883-1959; 1 volume (Box 43)
- Series 4. Court Records, 1858-1961
  - Assignment of wages, 1888-1939; 1 volume (Volume Item 46)
  - Justice of the Peace records, 1858, 1880-1886; 1 volume (Box 43)
  - Town court check book, 1952-1961 (Box 44)
- Series 5. Military Records, 1869-1940
  - Militia enrollments
    - 1869-1939, 1 volume (Box 43)
    - 1900-1911, 1 volume (Box 43)
  - Selective service registration index cards, circa 1940 (Box 47-48)
  - Selective service registration lists, 1940 October 25; 1 folder (Box 43)
- Series 6. School Records, 1846-1944
  - Building Committee construction records
    Includes agreements, correspondence, invoices, blueprints.
    - Lincoln School, 1912-1913 (Box 49)
    - Beecher St. School addition, 1921-1922 (Box 49)
    - Southington grade school, 1922-1926 (Box 49)
    - Plans for a six groom grade school, 1922 (Box 117)
  - Enumeration, 1894-1896; 1 volume (Box 49)
  - Minutes, 1846-1855; 1 volume (Box 49)
  - School registers, 1859-1882
    - 3rd District, 1859 November-1860 August; 1 volume (Box 50)
    - 3rd District, 1863 November-1865 August; 1 volume (Box 50)
    - 3rd District, 1865 November-1867 August; 1 volume (Box 50)
    - 3rd District, 1867 November-1869 April; 1 volume (Box 50)
    - 1st District, 1869 December-1870 July; 1 volume (Box 50)
    - 1st District, 1869 September-1870 July; 1 volume (Box 50)
    - 2nd District, 1869 October-1870 August; 1 volume (Box 50)
    - 3rd District, 1869 November-1870 July; 1 volume (Box 50)
    - 4th District, 1869 August-1870 June; 1 volume (Box 50)
    - 4th District Primary, 1869 November-1870 March; 1 volume (Box 50)
    - 1st District, 1870 April-June; 1 volume (Box 50)
    - 4th District Intermediate, 1869 August-1870 June; 1 volume (Box 50)
    - 5th District, 1869 November-1870 September; 1 volume (Box 50)
    - 6th District, 1869 October-1870 August; 1 volume (Box 50)
    - 1st District, 1869 October-1870 September; 1 volume (Box 50)
    - 8th District, 1869 November-1870 August; 1 volume (Box 50)
    - 9th District, 1869 October-1870 February; 1 volume (Box 50)
    - 9th District, 1870 April-August; 1 volume (Box 50)
    - 10th District, 1869 November-1870 April; 1 volume (Box 50)
    - 3rd District, 1881 September-1882 November; 1 volume (Box 50)
  - Treasurer's account book, 1874-1944; 1 volume (Box 50)
- Series 7. Election Records, 1940-1955
  - Voting lists
    - Men's, 1940 October 7; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - Women's, 1940 October 7; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - Men's, 1940 November 5; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - Women's, 1940 November 5; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - N-W, 1942 October 5; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - A-M, 1944 October 31; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - N-W, 1944 October 31; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - District 1, A-M, 1946 November 5; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - District 1, N-W, 1946 November 5; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - District 2, A-M, 1946 November 5; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - District 2, N-W, 1946 November 5; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - Special election, Town, District 1, 1947 October 6; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - Special election, Borough, District 1, 1947 October 6; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - District 1, A-M, 1948 October 4; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - District 1, N-W, 1948 October 4; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - District 2, A-M, 1948 October 4; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - District 2, N-W, 1948 October 4; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - District 1, A-M, 1948 November 2; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - District 1, N-W, 1948 November 2; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - District 2, A-M, 1948 November 2; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - District 2, N-W, 1948 November 2; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - District 1, A-M, 1949 April 23; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - District 1, N-W, 1949 April 23; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - District 2, A-M, 1949 April 23; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - District 2, N-W, 1949 April 23; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - District 2, N-W, 1950 November 7; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - A-M, undated; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - N-W, undated; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - 1955, 1 volume (Box 51)
- Series 8. Tax Records, 1792, 1899-1989
  - Appraisal of personal property
    - A-K, 1948; 1 volume (Box 52)
    - L-M, 1948; 1 volume (Box 52)
    - 1951, 1 volume (Box 52)
    - 1952, 1 volume (Box 52)
    - 1953, 1 volume (Box 52)
  - Individual tax lists
    - E-K, 1899; 1 volume (Volume Item 53)
    - E-L, 1907; 1 volume (Volume Item 54)
    - 1956
      - A-Bm, 1 volume (Volume Item 55)
        Volume number on spine: 1.
      - Bo-Ch, 1 volume (Volume Item 56)
        Volume number on spine: 2.
      - Ci-De, 1 volume (Volume Item 57)
        Volume number on spine: 3.
      - Di-F, 1 volume (Volume Item 58)
        Volume number on spine: 4.
      - G-H, 1 volume (Volume Item 59)
        Volume number on spine: 5.
      - I-La, 1 volume (Volume Item 60)
        Volume number on spine: 6.
      - Le-Me, 1 volume (Volume Item 61)
        Volume number on spine: 7.
      - Mi-O, 1 volume (Volume Item 62)
        Volume number on spine: 8.
      - P-R, 1 volume (Volume Item 63)
        Volume number on spine: 9.
      - Sa-Sp, 1 volume (Volume Item 64)
        Volume number on spine: 10.
      - St-V, 1 volume (Volume Item 65)
        Volume number on spine: 11.
      - W-Z and Developements, 1 volume (Volume Item 66)
        Volume number on spine: 12.
  - Old age assistance tax
    - 1936-1944
      - A-Ce, 1 volume (Volume Item 67)
      - Coa-Fr, 1 volume (Volume Item 68)
      - G-Kr, 1 volume (Volume Item 69)
      - La-O, 1 volume (Volume Item 70)
      - Pa-Sm, 1 volume (Volume Item 71)
      - So-Z, 1 volume (Volume Item 72)
      - Mc-R, 1 volume (Volume Item 73)
    - 1945-1946
      - Book 1, Academy - Belleview, 1 volume (Box 74)
      - Book 2, Berkley - Berlin, 1 volume (Box 74)
      - Book 3, Bishop - Burritt, 1 volume (Box 74)
      - Burwell - Churchill (Box 74)
      - Book 5, Clark - Eden (Box 74)
      - Book 6, Flanders - Highwood, 1 volume (Box 74)
      - Book 7, Hill - Liberty, 1 volume (Box 74)
      - Book 8, Liberty - Main, 1 volume (Box 74)
      - Book 9, Maple - Meriden, 1 volume (Box 75)
      - Book 10, Meriden & Waterbury - Mill, 1 volume (Box 75)
      - Book 11, Mine Hollow - North Main, 1 volume (Box 75)
      - Book 13, Queen - South Center, 1 volume (Box 75)
      - Book 14, South End - Spring., 1 volume (Box 75)
      - Book 16, Walnut - West, 1 volume (Box 75)
  - Rate books
    - 1931, 1932, 1933, 1934, 1936, 1937, 6 volumes (Box 76)
    - 1938, 1939, 1941, 1942, 1945, 1946, 6 volumes (Box 77)
  - Street assessments
    - 1899, 1 volume (Volume Item 78)
    - undated, 3 volumes (Volume Items 79-81)
  - Tax abstracts
    Tax abstracts starting in 1917 are not assigned box or item numbers. Researchers should request items by indicating year up to 1955, by indicating year and either automobilie or real property for 1956 to 1969 (for example, 1957 real property), or by indicating year and letter group for 1970 to 1989 (for example, 1979 A-I).
    Automobile and real property assessments are in different volumes starting in 1956.
    Volumes are labeled "Grand List" up to 1969.
    - 1792, undated (Box 117)
      Includes photostat copy of both the 1792 and the undated lists.
    - 1917, 1918, 1919, 1920, 1921, 1922, 1923, 1924, 1925, 1926, 1927, 1928, 1929, 1930, 1931, 1932, 1933, 1934, 1935, 1936, 1937, 1938, 1939, 1940, 1941, 1942, 1943, 1944, 1945, 1946, 1947, 1948, 1949, 1950, 1951, 1952, 1953, 1954, 1955, 39 volumes
    - Automobiles, 1956, 1957, 1959, 1960, 1961, 1962, 1963, 1969 L-Z; 8 volumes
      1969 A-K was not transferred to the Connecticut State Library.
    - Real property, 1956, 1957, 1958, 1959, 1960, 1961, 1962, 1963, 1964, 1966, 1967, 1968, 1969; 13 volumes
    - A-L, 1970; 1 volume
    - M-Z and personal property, 1970; 1 volume
    - A-L, 1971; 1 volume
    - M-Z and personal property, 1971; 1 volume
    - A-M, 1972; 1 volume
    - N-Z and personal property, 1972; 1 volume
    - A-L, 1973; 1 volume
    - M-Z and personal property, 1973; 1 volume
    - A-M, 1974; 1 volume
    - N-Z and personal property, 1974; 1 volume
    - A-M, 1975; 1 volume
    - N-Z and personal property, 1975; 1 volume
    - A-M, 1976; 1 volume
    - N-Z and personal property, 1976; 1 volume
    - A-M, 1977; 1 volume
    - N-Z and personal property, 1977; 1 volume
    - A-M, 1978; 1 volume
    - N-Z and personal property, 1978; 1 volume
    - A-I, 1979; 1 volume
    - J-R and personal property, 1979; 1 volume
    - S-Z and personal property, 1979; 1 volume
    - A-G, 1980; 1 volume
    - H-R, 1980; 1 volume
    - S-Z and personal property, 1980; 1 volume
    - A-G and personal property, 1981; 1 volume
    - H-R and personal property, 1981; 1 volume
    - S-Z and personal property, 1981; 1 volume
    - A-G, 1982; 1 volume
    - H-R, 1982; 1 volume
    - S-Z and personal property, 1982; 1 volume
    - A-G and personal property, 1983; 1 volume
    - H-R and personal property, 1983; 1 volume
    - S-Z and personal property, 1983; 1 volume
    - A-G and personal property, 1984; 1 volume
    - H-R and personal property, 1984; 1 volume
    - S-Z and personal property, 1984; 1 volume
    - A-G, 1985; 1 volume
    - H-P, 1985; 1 volume
    - Q-Z and personal property, 1985; 1 volume
    - A-G, 1986; 1 volume
    - H-R, 1986; 1 volume
    - S-Z and personal property, 1986; 1 volume
    - A-E and personal property, 1987; 1 volume
    - F-O, 1987; 1 volume
    - P-Z, 1987; 1 volume
    - A-E and personal property, 1988; 1 volume
    - F-O, 1988; 1 volume
    - P-Z, 1988; 1 volume
    - A-E and personal property, 1989; 1 volume
    - F-O, 1989; 1 volume
    - P-Z, 1989; 1 volume
  - Tax lien index cards, 1886-1888, 1931-1940 (Box 82)
- Series 9. Borough Records, 1890-1970; bulk 1900-1948
  - Agreements, 1919, 1926 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Annual reports, 1936, 1945 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Auditors, 1940-1945 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Bonds (Box 83)
    - Clerk, 1907-1923 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Constable, 1908-1917, 1931 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Policeman, 1915-1917, 1927-1932 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Sheriff, 1914-1931 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Tax Collector, 1907-1934 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Treasurer, 1907-1933 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous, 1921-1933 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Borough barn, 1946 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Borough meeting notes, 1939-1947 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Bus service, 1941-1945 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Charter, 1927-1944 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Claims for damages, Notices and releases of, 1912-1947 (Box 83, Folder 15-18)
  - Committees, 1942-1944, undated (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Complaints, 1937-1943, 1970, undated (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1925-1947, undated (Box 83, Folder 21-22)
  - Dump, 1941-1946, undated (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - Elections, 1943-1946 (Box 83, Folder 24-26)
  - Financial records, 1890-1948 (Box 83)